Focus your fear
Deadline is a drama, horror, thriller film directed by Sean McConville.
A screenwriter travels to an abandoned house to finish a script on time, but a
series of strange events lead her to a psychological breakdown.
Alice Evans, played by Brittany Murphy.
Lucy Woods, played by Thora Birch.
Rebecca, played by Tammy Blanchard.
David Woods, played by Marc Blucas.
David's Mother, played by Claudia Troll.
Deadline is a 2009 American psychological horror film directed by Sean
McConville and starring Brittany Murphy and Thora Birch.
The film explores themes of mental breakdown, writer, bathtub.
The tone is dark and intense and emotional.